=Just Fiancée= =Episode 8=
= مخطوبون فقط = = الحلقة 8 =
My goodness!
رباه!
I didn't think I would slap her.
لم أعتقد أنني سأصفعها.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Which hand did you slap her with?
بأي يد صفعتها؟
This one.
هذا.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I shouldn't have
لا يجب أن أمتلك
left you alone.
تركتك وحيدا.
It's OK.
كل شيء على مايرام.
I know you were busy.
أعلم أنك كنت مشغولا.
I understand.
أفهم.
There's nothing between Lin Shaoshao and I.
لا يوجد شيء بين أنا ولين شاوشاو.
The relationship between you and Lin Shaoshao
العلاقة بينك وبين لين شاوشاو
is none of my business.
ليس من أعمالي.
Does my relationship with her
هل علاقتي معها
have nothing to do with you?
لا علاقة لك؟
How does your relationship with her
كيف علاقتك معها
have anything to do with me?
هل لديك أي علاقة بي؟
Qiao Mai, aren't you...
كياو ماي ، أليس كذلك ...
jealous?
غيور؟
Not really.
ليس صحيحا.
Su Yu.
سو يو.
Su Yu!
سو يو!
What?
ماذا؟
Come closer.
اقترب.
I know she is only
انا اعلم انها فقط
your friend.
صديقك.
And I'm
و انا
your fiancée.
خطيبتك.
Unfortunately, I'm a fake!
لسوء الحظ ، أنا مزيف!
You're real for me!
أنت حقيقي بالنسبة لي!
(Mom)
(أم)
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Mai!
مايو!
A man named Lin Duoduo
رجل اسمه لين دودو
came to our home just now
أتيت إلى منزلنا الآن
with a picture of another girl
مع صورة فتاة أخرى
who looks just like you!
من يشبهك تماما!
Did you tell him anything about me?
هل أخبرته بأي شيء عني؟
Of course not!
بالطبع لا!
I kept my lips sealed!
أبقيت شفتي مغلقة!
That's good.
هذا جيد.
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
A man named Lin Duoduo
رجل اسمه لين دودو
came to my home just now
أتيت إلى منزلي الآن
with Gu Manman's picture.
مع صورة Gu Manman.
What?
ماذا؟
(Qiao Mai's home) Mom, where did that man go?
(منزل كياو ماي) أمي ، أين ذهب هذا الرجل؟
He already left.
(منزل كياو ماي) لقد غادر بالفعل.
He left two photos on the table.
لقد ترك صورتين على الطاولة.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
How did Lin Duoduo
كيف فعل لين دودو
manage to locate your home?
تمكنت من تحديد موقع منزلك؟
I don't know.
لا أعلم.
I have a feeling
لدي شعور
Grandpa might find out sooner or later.
قد يكتشف الجد عاجلاً أم آجلاً.
Maybe we should tell him now.
ربما يجب أن نخبره الآن.
No.
رقم.
I told you.
أخبرتك.
Grandpa hasn't had his operation yet.
الجد لم يخضع لعملية جراحية بعد.
We have to continue the lie.
علينا أن نواصل الكذب.
But now
لكن الآن
so many people know about this.
يعرف الكثير من الناس عن هذا.
They even managed to find my home!
حتى أنهم تمكنوا من العثور على منزلي!
Why don't we tell Grandpa ourselves?
لماذا لا نخبر الجد بأنفسنا؟
Are you sure about that?
هل انت متاكد من ذلك؟
Look at you two lovebirds!
انظروا إليكم طائرا حب!
Why are you two so happy?
لماذا أنتما الاثنان سعيدان جدا؟
Share it with Grandpa!
شاركها مع الجد!
You tell him.
أخبره.
Tell me already!
قل لي بالفعل!
Come on!
هيا!
You should tell him.
يجب أن تخبره.
Grandpa!
جدي!
If someone lied to you,
إذا كذب عليك شخص ما ،
what would you do?
ماذا كنت ستفعل؟
I hate
انا اكره
dishonest people the most!
أكثر الناس غير الشرفاء!
Those who lie to me
أولئك الذين يكذبون علي
will never be forgiven!
لن يغفر ابدا!
But,
ولكن،
Manman,
الأم،
I'm sure you are an honest girl.
أنا متأكد من أنك فتاة صادقة.
I never lie!
أنا لا أكذب أبدا!
And I believe Yu won't lie to me.
وأعتقد أن يو لن يكذب علي.
No, I won't.
لا ، لن أفعل.
I'm an honest man.
أنا رجل نزيه.
Grandpa,
الجد
we need to take care of something.
نحن بحاجة لرعاية شيء ما.
We'll go to our room.
سنذهب إلى غرفتنا.
You should rest early!
يجب أن ترتاح مبكرا!
How did Lin Duoduo find your home?
كيف وجد Lin Duoduo منزلك؟
What if Grandpa
ماذا لو الجد
found out about it?
اكتشفت ذلك؟
Maybe I should talk to Lin Duoduo?
ربما يجب أن أتحدث إلى Lin Duoduo؟
No, Lin Duoduo
لا ، لين دودو
doesn't care
لا يهتم
whether you are Qiao Mai or Gu Manman
سواء كنت تشياو ماي أو جو مانمان
since you two look exactly the same.
لأنكما تبدوان متشابهين تمامًا.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I will act just like Gu Manman.
سوف أتصرف مثل Gu Manman.
No, I won't allow it.
لا ، لن أسمح بذلك.
Why?
لماذا ا؟
Lin Duoduo likes Gu Manman
يحب Lin Duoduo Gu Manman
for her beautiful face.
لوجهها الجميل.
But I like you.
لكن انا معجب بك.
I don't want you to meet him.
لا أريدك أن تقابله.
But...
ولكن...
No buts.
لا لكن.
Come on,
هيا،
he has found my home!
لقد وجد بيتي!
Trust me!
صدقني!
I will act just like her.
سوف أتصرف مثلها تماما.
No!
رقم!
You are nothing like Gu Manman!
أنت لست مثل Gu Manman!
He will notice it at first sight!
سوف يلاحظ ذلك من النظرة الأولى!
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I knew it!
كنت أعرف!
I am nothing to you all.
أنا لا شيء لكم جميعا.